I
我
this lesson we're gonna be looking at solving a problem
这节课我们要学习解决一个问题
in the composition
在构图中
we have two components
我们有两个组成部分
h to AP calls
h到AP呼叫
a bunch of metro code that usually you need to write around these AP calls
一堆metro代码，通常需要围绕这些AP调用编写
usually our promises
通常是我们的承诺
needed check for when it's loading are not loading are done loading
需要检查的时候，它的装载是不装载完成装载
if there's any errors that pop up
如果出现任何错误
usually what you end up doing in your code is creating another file that encapsulate this behavior
通常，您在代码中所做的就是创建另一个封装此行为的文件
arcades will be moving some of that shared code into a file called
拱廊将将其中的一些共享代码移动到一个名为
our composer directory
我们的作曲家目录
I'll be more clear in our code example
我将在我们的代码示例中更加清楚
let's dive into it
让我们深入研究一下
here we have a single component which has a search input
这里我们有一个单独的组件，它有一个搜索输入
and for now we're just printing out the loading status the error status
现在我们只是打印出加载状态错误状态
the number of events that matched the search input
与搜索输入匹配的事件数
we're not actually returning the results just the number of results
我们实际上并不是返回结果只是返回结果的数量
in the browser this is what this template is going to look like
在浏览器中，这就是模板的外观
further down in the file
在档案的后面
you can see that we are importing
你可以看到我们正在进口
using our composition a p I so we're in view to using the composition a p I plug in
使用我们的compositionapi，这样我们就可以使用compositionapi插件了
also using this dummy event AP file which
同时使用这个虚拟事件AP文件
don't need to read
不需要阅读
we have inside of our setup method
我们有内部的设置方法
reactive references
反应性参考
our search input
我们的搜索输入
results
结果
loading
加载
and our state
我们的国家呢
and they each have an initial value
它们都有一个初始值
next we have our load data asynchronous function which is called whenever a search input changes
接下来我们有加载数据异步函数，当搜索输入发生变化时调用它
she said loading to true we reset the error and results values
她说我们重新设置了结果
we do our AP call
我们打AP电话
return we said
我们说了回来
result value
结果值
the errors are caught
错误被发现了
then finally
最后呢
he said loading value equal to false
他说装载值等于假
now we have a little bit of code to write
现在我们有一点代码要写
want to watch our search input
想看看我们的搜索输入吗
when it changes first we check to see if our value is not empty if it's not empty
当它第一次改变时，我们检查它的值是否不为空
go ahead and call load data with their search input value
继续使用搜索输入值调用加载数据
otherwise of our search input is empty
否则我们的搜索输入是空的
the results
结果
lastly we need to return the items that our template needs access to
最后，我们需要返回模板需要访问的项
jump in the browser we can see that as we type into the search field
跳进浏览器，我们可以看到，当我们输入搜索字段
loading gets toggled
加载被切换
the number of events gets return
返回事件数
works great but let's modular eyes the code around are a p I call so that we can reuse this
工作很好，但让我们模块化的眼睛周围的代码是一个p I调用，以便我们可以重用它
other components
其他部件
do this
做这个
I am going to copy some of the code in our component
我将复制组件中的一些代码
I am going to leave this code except for
我要留下这个代码除了
the AP call
美联社电话
which is specific to this component
特定于此组件
then I'm gonna jump into the use promise j s file which I just created
然后我将跳转到我刚刚创建的use promise j s文件中
inside the file I'm gonna import
在我要导入的文件里面
composition a p I
成分a p I
I'll create a function called you
我将创建一个名为you的函数
which receives
它接收
function to call with a sink away
函数调用时使用接收器
basically are a p I call
基本上都是我打给你的
based on our code here but it needs some modifications
基于我们这里的代码，但它需要一些修改
we're going to create a
我们要创建一个
create promise
创造承诺
which will contain
它将包含
asynchronous
异步
anonymous function
匿名函数
which receives any arguments that are a p I called needs
它接收的任何参数都是我称为需要的p
then instead of
而不是
the AP call here
这里是美联社的电话
this is where we call the function we passed in earlier
这就是我们调用之前传递的函数的地方
with
具有
arguments we said then
我们当时说的论点
our case will have a single argument which is the value of the search input
我们的案例将有一个参数，即搜索输入的值
lastly we will return results
最后我们将返回结果
loading error
加载错误
as well as our create promise function
以及我们的创建承诺功能
back in side of our apt view we can import
回到我们正确的观点，我们可以导入
use promise
使用承诺
I
我
then we'll create a new constant called and get event
然后我们将创建一个新的常量，称为get event
which calls used promise
这叫用过的承诺
has a single parameter which is search
只有一个参数是search
execute the AP I call specific to this component
执行特定于此组件的AP I call
get our vet count
去查一下兽医
our search value
我们的搜索值
and inside of watch
以及手表内部
now when the search input changes
现在当搜索输入改变时
need to call and get event
需要打电话获取事件
God
上帝
promise
承诺
in our search input
在我们的搜索输入中
results
结果
now inside get events
现在，在获取事件中
we need to reset them
我们需要重置它们
lastly results are and loading
最后的结果是和加载
restructured from the event object
从事件对象重新构造
if I jump into the browser
如果我跳进浏览器
I can see that everything is still working
我看得出一切都还在工作
now my code is more reusable
现在我的代码更可重用了
when I showed this code to two different members of the Vue core team
当我向Vue核心团队的两个不同成员展示这段代码时
I wanted to me to make a change
我想让我改变一下
basically said hey
基本上是说嘿
keep the return values named spaced
保留名为spaced的返回值
and are the object get event
对象获取事件
structure
结构
if I did this
如果我这么做的话
code would change to look like this
代码会变成这样
where I have been taught to get it on
在那里我被教导要穿上它
other day is a little more encapsulated and it's clear where it's coming from
前几天有了一点封装，很清楚它是从哪里来的
however if we look in a browser
但是如果我们在浏览器中查看
can see that it's not working
可以看出它不起作用
us in recognizing that these are reactive references in calling dot value on them
我们认识到这些是在调用它们的点值时的反应性引用
fix this
解决这个问题
due to using the composition AP aye we could just call dot value on each of those items in the template
由于使用合成方法，我们可以在模板中的每一项上调用点值
I'll be the solution here
我来解决这个问题
however
然而
I did want to validate if this worked or didn't work in
我确实想验证一下这是否有效
I fired up some code of you three and sure enough
我启动了你们三个的密码，果然
this code would work
这个代码可以用
as expected with you three you wouldn't have to call dot value it would recognise them as reactive record
正如你所期望的那样，你不必调用点值，它会将它们识别为反应性记录
it seems to be a bug in the composition API plugin for
它似乎是
you
你
I
我
gratulations you get to the end of the view three essentials course I am now going to go work on the view three reactivity course which by the time you're watching this male
大家好了，视图三要素课程结束了，我现在要学习视图三反应性课程，当你们看到这个男性的时候
oh
哦
either going to it or keep an eye out for it
要么去，要么留心
the other
其他的
ah
啊
and again
再说一遍
get through the course
完成课程